# **LUCKY SINGH**

## Front End Developer / UI Developer







Ls170693@gmail.com 📞 +91 7976645391 👽 J-1102, ACH Society, Sec 76, Noida (UP)



in <u>Linkdin</u>

### PERSONAL STATEMENT

Front End Developer with **4.5+** years of experience working with JavaScript, jQuery ,HTML/CSS with modern technologies to deliver exceptional customer experiences. Adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions, and determining user satisfaction.

### **EXPERIENCE**



# 📥 Z1 TECH (Remote)

Front End Developer (June 2022 - Nov 2023) Gurugram Worked on multiple products in Z1 tech like job portals ,blog websites, organization internal products, and ensured the overall UI and performance of the product worked fine.

### key responsibility

- Implemented and maintained overall websites UI.
- Optimized page elements to reduce loading time and debugged code to ensure cross-browser usability.
- Implemented and tested websites functionality to ensure successful operations across all platforms.
- Implemented responsive design for improved mobile experience.
- Work closely with backend team to meet project requirements, goals, and desired functionality.

### FreeKaaMaal.com

Front End Developer (May 2019 - June 2022) Noida Implemented multiple projects using HTML/CSS, and JavaScript Create self-contained, reusable, and testable modules and components

### key responsibility

- Convert PSD or Adobe XD file into actual code using html CSS and JavaScript to developed new web pages for freekaamaal project.
- Worked closely with UX designer and backend team to deliver an overall seamless user experience.
- Implemented responsive web pages Optimizing sites for maximum speed and scalability.
- Implemented best practices for Optimizing websites speed and SEO.

### **SKILLS**

- Front End Development
  - JavaScript
  - ReactIS
  - jQuery
  - GIT
  - Wordpress
  - SCSS
  - Bootstrap
  - CSS
  - HTML

### **EDUCATION**

Master's in computer application at Sharda university Gr. Noida (2015-2017).

**Bachelors in computer application** at maharaja Ganga Singh university suratgarh (Raj) (2011-2014).

**12th** from ajmer board suratgarh (Raj).

# **PROJECT PREVIEW**

FreeKaaMaal <u>Jnee</u> <u>Findanyanswer</u> <u>Receptix</u> Woost.io <u>Articlepost</u>